MY PHONE
IT'S ON MY DESK
BRING IT!
Kannawa-san?
My phone!
I'm tellin' ya to bring it to me!
Y-Y-Yes, ma'am!
Why are you spacing out, Kamegawa?
Did Kannawa-senpai get mad at you?
Well, that's partially true.
Partially?
Oh, no...
I noticed Senpai's dialect slips out
when she gets flustered.
She did it just a bit ago.
Dialect?
Oh! I need to head back.
I'll catch you later.
Okay.
Dialect, huh?
I haven't heard her using
a dialect at all, though.
MY AWKWARD SENPAI
EPISODE 7: MOM'S COMIN' TO VISIT!
"Mom's Comin' to Visit!"
You've been sighing for a while.
Cut it out. It's making me feel down.
I-I'm sorry.
My parents have been messaging me nonstop,
even after I told them
I can't reply when I'm working.
You're still a kid if you feel annoyed
about your parents reaching out.
You don't understand what a blessing it is.
You're absolutely right.
I did it again!
I could have said that in a nicer way!
YU-CHAN
Do your parents call you "Yu-chan"?
Don't be late to our next meeting,
Yu-chan.
I knew you'd say that!
Just messing with you.
You should go visit your family sometime.
I guess I could visit this weekend.
I don't have any plans.
Do they live near here?
They live in Kawaguchi City, in Saitama.
That's close!
Which is why they sometimes
come to check in on me.
They nag at me to cook my own
meals or to clean and such.
It's not always nice that they live so close.
I see. That can be a lot...
Yu-chan.
Hey!
That being said...
I wouldn't want my parents to
see me livin' alone like this.
I'm glad my hometown's
all the way in Kyushu.
Time to go shopping.
NAKA STREET SHOPPING DISTRICT
BIG BARGAIN SALE
I haven't been here in a while.
What should I get?
WAGYU FAIR
That's right! This is what it's all about!
I can eat whatever I want, whenever I want!
This is the true pleasure of living alone!
LIMITED-TIME SALE! BENTO BOXES
This is it!
It can't be helped, since it's a limited sale.
If they're offerin' such a kindness,
I gotta take advantage of it.
Huh? Kannawa-senpai?
What?!
What are you doing here?!
I come here sometimes,
since it's in my neighborhood.
Shoot!
I forgot!
Senpai?
Wait a minute.
Didn't you say you were
going to visit your family?
I thought I would,
But it turns out they took
off on vacation today.
I didn't know you shopped at this store, too.
Yeah I... Sometimes...
What are you shopping for?
The veggies here are pretty cheap.
I... I see.
Shoot...
I only came here to buy bento.
He's gonna find out that I don't cook!
Tonight's menu is teriyaki tuna
and deep-fried eggplant.
Oh! Make that one thing, too.
The fluffy thing.
You mean the yam okonomiyaki?
You really do like that stuff.
Yeah, I really do.
I could eat it for every meal.
He looks super jealous of them.
Well, of course he does.
Could it be that Senpai
and I look like a couple?
Wait, what am I thinking?
Hey, do you...
It's admirable that you do your own cooking,
but are there times you wish you
had a girlfriend who's a good cook?
Huh?
Why did I just ask that?
Hmm... Well...
Being a good cook is a nice thing.
But...
Being able to cook together,
or if someone who usually never cooks
spends time practicing cooking for me...
That would be...
Yeah! That would be nice... I think.
Speaking of which...
What did you come to buy, Senpai?
V-Vegetables!
Oh! I heard mustard spinach is on sale today.
MUSTARD SPINACH SALE
I...
I see...
Good work!
TO THE CORPORATION
There.
Oh. Good work.
Sorry to dump the meeting
for the collab café on you.
Did it go well?
It did.
We finalized the merchandise lineup,
as well as the restaurant's layout...
Wait... Senpai!
What happened to your hand?!
Oh, these?
Th-They're just paper cuts!
Don't worry, I'm fine now.
Is it even possible to
get that many paper cuts?
MOM
Ugh.
I told her not to call me on weekdays!
Just ignore her.
You're still a kid if you feel annoyed
about your parents reaching out.
You don't understand what a blessing it is.
Sorry, but could you fix this for me?
Huh? Oh... Sure.
Hello?
Hold on.
I'm going somewhere I can talk to you.
Fix this?
Hello.
You finally answered, Azusa-chan!
I've called you so many times now.
Yeah, yeah.
Listen.
Remember Sayo-chan next door?
Her grandbaby was born just yesterday!
Things seem to be goin' well there, and I just...
I told ya, stop callin' me on my work days!
Oh, sorry, dear!
I only wanted to ask ya
something important, that's all.
Fine. Just one thing.
'Kay!
Are ya by any chance... dating anyone?
What?
Y'know how you asked me to send ya
a pic of the yukata the other day?
That's when my motherly intuition kicked in.
Wh-What's that even mean?
Oh, if you're not, that's fine, too!
If push comes to shove,
arranged marriage is an option.
I have a boyfriend, so there's no need.
Huh?! Wait! You do?!
What's he li—
I-I'm sorry. I didn't mean to eavesdrop...
I know you told me to fix this,
but it's still got some ink, so I don't know
what exactly needs to be fixed...
Huh?
No, I wanted you to fix it
back where it belongs...
Wait. Is "fix" dialect?
Oh! Is that what that was?
I'm sorry! I didn't realize.
No, that was on me.
I'm sorry.
"To fix" means "to put away," so...
Oh, it's okay!
I sometimes look up your dialect,
but this time I took it too literally.
What?
D-Do I speak in my dialect that often?
I was doin' my best to speak in standard
Japanese to avoid work-related issues...
Could it be that there were
times something I said
didn't parse well just 'cuz I didn't realize?!
Oh...
So there were?!
N-No, there weren't!
Please don't worry!
Sorry...
There were... actually a few.
Figures.
Um, Senpai—
Kamegawa!
Yes?
From now on, if something I say
doesn't make sense, tell me.
Please.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
The person Senpai's dating...
MOM
Again?
Hello?
Oh! Azusa-chan!
I told ya, I'm workin'!
I forgot to tell ya an important thing.
I'm in front of your house right now.
What?!
Huh?!
What time are ya off work?
If it's possible, I'm thinkin'
we can go out to eat
with that boyfriend of yours
that you mentioned.
Hello? Did ya hear me? Azusa?
What?!
Are you all right, Senpai?
My mother appears to be...
at my house.
What? Right now?
And she...
asked if I could go out to eat
with her and my boyfriend.
Huh?
Th-That's great!
It's not!
I don't...
What?
I don't even have a boyfriend.
Why am I relieved?!
I'm being so rude!
This isn't good...
At this rate, she's going to
hook me up with a stranger.
Um...
What if I pretend to be your boyfriend?
Finally finished.
Let's go home.
Yeah! This week was rough.
Sure was.
Let's do this.
Right.
WE ARE COWORKERS
Okay, firstly,
our story is that we're coworkers.
Got it?
Yes, ma'am. Understood.
Also...
What else do we need to decide on?
Um...
Maybe how long we've been dating?
One week!
That's rather recent.
Well... I don't know much
about this kind of thing.
I mean, I don't know a lot, either.
How about four months?
Why four months?
I was thinking that it's been
four months since I met you.
Actually, it's been longer than that...
I see.
A strategy to skillfully blend in the facts.
Got it! What else?
Um...
Establishing the scenario is important,
but I actually don't know much about you.
Like your hobbies, or what
you do on weekends.
I feel like I'd be able to answer
your mom's questions better
if I knew those kinds of things.
Oh, if it's difficult to say, then—
My hobby is gaming.
Oh, really?
Me, too!
I just started playing Final Fantasy VII Rebirth,
and I'm only in the early stages,
but the areas are so vast!
I was having fun just exploring,
and before I knew it, two hours had passed!
I get you!
I tell myself that I'll work on the main story,
but then I get distracted by all the little
details and end up straying away.
But that's what makes it fun!
We have a hobby in common! Nice!
Yes!
Okay! We can get through the rest somehow!
Yes, ma'am! I'll do my best!
Is my tie straight?
Is the color okay?
You're too nervous.
Don't worry about these things.
We'll just go as planned.
Oh, there you are.
Sorry to keep you two waiting!
I-Is she your sister?
She's my mother.
A cousin?
My mother!
AZUSA'S MOTHER - SAKURA KANNAWA
Sorry for inviting you two out so suddenly.
You must be Azusa's boyfriend.
This is Yu Kamegawa-san.
He's also my coworker.
I'm Kamegawa!
It's nice to meet you!
The pleasure is mine.
This is the first time my daughter's
introduced me to a boyfriend!
I'm so happy.
And then she thought she was real
mature and ordered the spicy ramen!
She didn't have to finish it,
but she kept goin' with tears in her eyes.
So silly of her!
Hey, Mom!
She's so stubborn, just like her father.
Oh, yeah.
Kamegawa-san!
What part about her were you drawn to?
What?
Huh?! Don't ask such a weird question!
What about it is weird?
He's your boyfriend, right?
I wanna know.
There's no way he can answer that!
Senp—
Azusa...san...
Sorry, I need to answer this.
It's a client.
Oh, of course.
She works so hard.
She does.
So?
What's really goin' on between you two?
Huh?
W-Well, um...
'Cuz, you know...
She's good-looking, right?
Y-Yes.
I'm worried about her.
Since she's such an introvert,
what if she's gettin' scammed out there?
Oh, I highly doubt she is...
Really?
You're not thinkin' of
swindlin' her or anything?
I'm not!
She's only really interested in games.
I'm sure she has money because of that.
Um... I said I'm not interested in that.
Could it be that you two have a child?!
We don't!
We really don't! We're fine!
Oh, of course!
You two have that feelin' about ya.
You're so quick to shift gears!
Sorry.
I just can't help it, knowin' how she is.
I bet she's tough on the folks
around her at work, too, right?
Huh? Well, uh...
When she was a kid, she was
simply a shy, reserved girl.
In elementary school,
she was elected to be the class
representative for her good grades.
She did the best she could in her own way,
but nothing can be that easy.
During practice for sports day,
one of her classmates got hurt
while messin' around.
She felt responsible for not doin' a good job,
and she ended up yellin',
"Calm down!" to everyone.
From then on, everyone around
her was scared of her.
But that got me thinkin'.
That awkward girl...
It's her unrelenting kindness that made her
determined to protect her classmates,
even at the cost of them hatin' her.
I guess it's hard to understand
where I'm coming from.
I know she should be more
put-together at her age,
but please don't hate her.
I don't.
There's no way I would ever hate Senpai.
It's true that her words can be harsh,
and that there are people
around her who say she's scary.
But she's only doing that to warn me
before I can mess anything up.
And if I do things correctly,
she makes sure to praise me.
I know that at the end of it all,
she's a genuinely kind person.
You're so sweet!
Now I'm feeling all happy!
Just the other day she...
Thank you...
Sorry to keep you until this hour,
but I had a lot of fun.
No, no. The pleasure's mine.
Oh, that's right.
Thanks for playing along for her sake.
Huh?
You're not really her boyfriend, are you?
Uh, well...
You called Azusa "Senpai," after all.
Still...
I'm relieved to know she has someone
as responsible as you by her side.
Not at all!
I need to do better at my job.
Even today, I couldn't understand
Senpai's dialect—I mean, vocabulary—
and caused problems...
Huh?
Mom!
The taxi's here.
Coming!
One more thing.
Sorry for the hold-up!
Get back home safely.
Yeah. See you tomorrow.
Now, eat up.
It's to thank you for
sticking with me yesterday.
Thank you so much!
Let's eat!
Thank you for waiting.
Here is the pasta lunch.
I can't cut this.
If it's okay with you, can I have that?
Huh?
Oh... Do you like tomatoes?
Oh, well... as much as anyone, I guess...
I mean, yes! I do!
They're my favorite.
Um, sorry.
When you say "cut," it means
"eat" in the Kyushu dialect, right?
So "I can't cut" means "I can't eat..."
In other words, you don't like tomatoes.
How did you—
You're too well-versed in that dialect!
Not at all.
Your Kyushu dialect is hard to study
since it's mixed with other
dialects from that area.
A-Anyway!
What did you talk to my
mother about yesterday?
Huh?
During our ride home, she kept
trying to dig up information on you.
It was a lot to handle!
W-Well...
The fact that she speaks to you in
our dialect must mean she trusts ya.
We didn't... talk about anything much.
What's with that face? You're lying!
You think it's okay to lie
to your mentor like that?!
Well, then, it's a secret.
What?! That's even more unforgivable!
Come on, now...
Oh, it looks like we get a drink after our meal.
Don't change the subject!